Pravinkumar Purohit

D-504, Madhuvan Glory, Nr.Shree Ram Chowk, New Naroda Ahmedabad, Gujarat, 382330 (982) 531-5641 pravin.purohit121984@outlook.com

CAREER OBJECTIVE

Skilled customer service professional with 14.5+ years of successful management and leadership experience Dedicated to bettering the customer experience with reliable product education, timely assistance, helpful feedback, and respectful conflict management response. Confident communicator with the ability to lead colleagues, respond to customer inquiries, and mediate conflict. Enthusiastic and personable individual who enjoys working with people and building long-lasting relationships and product loyalty. Passionate about creating organizational success and bettering brand reputation through serving customers in a truly memorable way.

EXPERIENCE

ANEEV TRAVELS PRIVATE LIMITED, Ahmedabad, Gujarat

Director, Mar 2019 - Present

- Work professionally in providing travel services to clients
- Manage workflow and processes in Company
- A team player with a high level of flexibility
- Offer best travel options in term of pricing and routing
- Maintain a high level of customer service by "Going the Extra Mile"
- Manage all Travel products and query of Clients

MAMATA AIRWINGS, Ahmedabad, Gujarat

Sr. Executive. "International Ticketing & Visas", Jun 2008 - Feb 2019

- Booked international and domestic airline reservations,
- Handling Eurail booking.
- Help clients in getting Visitor or Business visa for different countries

I CALL INDIA PVT. LTD., Ahmedabad, Gujarat

Customer Care Executive May 2007 - Apr 2008

- Responding promptly to customer inquiries.
- · Handle customer complaints actively and resolve them on time
- Ensure the quality of services is maintained. Communicating with customers through various channels. Ensure customer satisfaction and provide professional customer support.

VAIBHAV TRAVELS, Ahmedabad, Gujarat

Office Executive, May 2006 - Jun 2007

- Handling Visitor, Business Visa. •
- Handling Passport Query •
- 1Handling Domestic and International Air Ticketing

EDUCATION

Gujarat University

Ahmedabad, Gujarat

Bachelor of Arts (B.A.) English Literature (May 2006)

IITC GLOBAL CAREERS WORLD AHMEDABAD, GUJARAT

IATA foundation Diploma Course IATA foundation Diploma Course

CERTIFICATIONS

- Galileo CRS Certificate
- Amadeus CRS Certificate
- TRS & TAAI Certificate of Travel Sales Consultant
- TRS & TAAI Certificate of Key Account Management Professional
- TRS & TAAI certificate of Customer Service Professional